<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Aleo</string>
    <string name="need_network">Network access is required for the application to work</string>
    <string name="try_again">Try again</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="explorer_menu_item">Explorer</string>
    <string name="education_menu_item">Education</string>
    <string name="faq_menu_item">FAQ</string>
    <string name="lecture_number">Lecture number</string>
    <string name="question">Question</string>
    <string name="answer">Answer</string>
    <string name="logoplaceholder">logoPlaceHolder</string>
    <string name="from">"   from   "</string>

    <!-- Questions usual. -->
    <string name="question1">What is Aleo?</string>
    <string name="question2">What is the idea for the project?</string>
    <string name="question3">Where can I see the entire Aleo ecosystem?</string>
    <string name="question4">What is ZK?</string>
    <string name="question5">What consensus mechanism does Aleo use?</string>
    <string name="question6">If a protocol allows you to create applications,
        then it should have its own programming language, right?</string>
    <string name="question7">Should this language have its own development environment?</string>
    <string name="question8">How is Aleo different from Zcash, Monero?</string>
    <string name="question9">What about investors?</string>
    <string name="question10">What is the status of the Aleo ambassador program?</string>
    <string name="question11">What types of activities can I do?</string>
    <string name="question12">Where to send my activities?</string>
    <string name="question13">Where can I get materials (logos, backgrounds, color palette) for my
        future works?</string>
    <string name="question14">What about rewards?</string>
    <string name="question15">How to creat wallet in aleo network?</string>
    <string name="question16">When and where will it be possible to buy Aleo tokens?</string>
    <string name="question17">What will Aleo coins be used for?</string>
    <string name="question18">Who is Aleo Voyager?</string>
    <string name="question19">What are grants?</string>
    <string name="question20">Is there any documentations on how to set up a node and join
        testnet 3?</string>
    <string name="question21">What is Aleo Education?</string>

    <!-- Questions from discord -->
    <string name="question22">Hello everyone, what do you need to do to become an
        ambassador?</string>
    <string name="question23">Hi all. What is the no 3 test, in installing a node for mining
        equipment from a video card?</string>
    <string name="question24">How to create a wallet to receive rewards from a node?</string>
    <string name="question25">Hi, what do you use when creating infographics?</string>
    <string name="question26">Voyager is between apprentice and maestro turns out?</string>
    <string name="question27">Guys, tell me, KYC will be possible to pass the Russian
        Federation?</string>
    <string name="question28">Did I understand correctly that if I just want to keep uptime,
        is it enough to have the prover turned on? If I want to mine,
        do I need to turn off the prover and start the Aleo client?</string>
    <string name="question29">Does the testnet still work?</string>
    <string name="question30">Guys I have a question, I need help. On which Fireside or Community
        Call can I present my project in English?)</string>
    <string name="question31">I mine on three cards 3080, the hashrate in the miner writes 2000
        from each one. But in the statistics on damominer.hk 3.03K P/s is displayed,
        it should be 6K P/s, or not?</string>
    <string name="question32">Hi all. On the website of the danomainer, they write connect to our
        pool and you can dig without your own node. It begs the question. If you have your own node,
        can you connect to it?</string>
    <string name="question33">If you take a GTX 1060 3 gb ti for mining and put it on mining.
        How many coins will she bring in a month? And in general, does it make sense to put this
        video for mining? I just see that everyone puts on 3090.
        So I asked myself this question.</string>
    <string name="question34">Greetings. This question has probably been asked before,
        but I will ask again. Can anyone explain why they give the role of ambassadors and generally
        keep the RU branch if the Russian Federation is in the bath?</string>
    <string name="question35">I try to catch the logic, 32 RAM or 40 which is better? I mean,
        as I saw in the requirements, it’s always 8,16,32,64, so I think if you take 40 it will be
        better or 32 or 64, that is, that the gap between them will not change
        the weather or not?</string>
    <string name="question36">Is using multiple servers with 24 threads, say 2 servers 24=48,
        is it the same as using one server with 48 threads?</string>
    <string name="question37">Guys, is there an option like in fish to limit the number
        of threads used?</string>





</resources>