<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Aleo</string>
    <string name="need_network">Network access is required for the application to work</string>
    <string name="try_again">Try again</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="explorer_menu_item">Explorer</string>
    <string name="education_menu_item">Education</string>
    <string name="faq_menu_item">FAQ</string>
    <string name="lecture_number">Lecture number</string>
    <string name="question">Question</string>
    <string name="answer">Answer</string>
    <string name="logoplaceholder">logoPlaceHolder</string>
    <string name="from">"   from   "</string>

    <!-- Questions usual. -->
    <string name="question1">What is Aleo?</string>
    <string name="question2">What is the idea for the project?</string>
    <string name="question3">Where can I see the entire Aleo ecosystem?</string>
    <string name="question4">What is ZK?</string>
    <string name="question5">What consensus mechanism does Aleo use?</string>
    <string name="question6">If a protocol allows you to create applications,
        then it should have its own programming language, right?</string>
    <string name="question7">Should this language have its own development environment?</string>
    <string name="question8">How is Aleo different from Zcash, Monero?</string>
    <string name="question9">What about investors?</string>
    <string name="question10">What is the status of the Aleo ambassador program?</string>
    <string name="question11">What types of activities can I do?</string>
    <string name="question12">Where to send my activities?</string>
    <string name="question13">Where can I get materials (logos, backgrounds, color palette) for my
        future works?</string>
    <string name="question14">What about rewards?</string>
    <string name="question15">How to creat wallet in aleo network?</string>
    <string name="question16">When and where will it be possible to buy Aleo tokens?</string>
    <string name="question17">What will Aleo coins be used for?</string>
    <string name="question18">Who is Aleo Voyager?</string>
    <string name="question19">What are grants?</string>
    <string name="question20">Is there any documentations on how to set up a node and join
        testnet 3?</string>
    <string name="question21">What is Aleo Education?</string>

    <!-- Questions from discord -->
    <string name="question22">Hello everyone, what do you need to do to become an
        ambassador?</string>
    <string name="question23">Hi all. What is the no 3 test, in installing a node for mining
        equipment from a video card?</string>
    <string name="question24">How to create a wallet to receive rewards from a node?</string>
    <string name="question25">Hi, what do you use when creating infographics?</string>
    <string name="question26">Voyager is between apprentice and maestro turns out?</string>
    <string name="question27">Guys, tell me, KYC will be possible to pass the Russian
        Federation?</string>
    <string name="question28">Did I understand correctly that if I just want to keep uptime,
        is it enough to have the prover turned on? If I want to mine,
        do I need to turn off the prover and start the Aleo client?</string>
    <string name="question29">Does the testnet still work?</string>
    <string name="question30">Guys I have a question, I need help. On which Fireside or Community
        Call can I present my project in English?)</string>
    <string name="question31">I mine on three cards 3080, the hashrate in the miner writes 2000
        from each one. But in the statistics on damominer.hk 3.03K P/s is displayed,
        it should be 6K P/s, or not?</string>
    <string name="question32">Hi all. On the website of the danomainer, they write connect to our
        pool and you can dig without your own node. It begs the question. If you have your own node,
        can you connect to it?</string>
    <string name="question33">If you take a GTX 1060 3 gb ti for mining and put it on mining.
        How many coins will she bring in a month? And in general, does it make sense to put this
        video for mining? I just see that everyone puts on 3090.
        So I asked myself this question.</string>
    <string name="question34">Greetings. This question has probably been asked before,
        but I will ask again. Can anyone explain why they give the role of ambassadors and generally
        keep the RU branch if the Russian Federation is in the bath?</string>
    <string name="question35">I try to catch the logic, 32 RAM or 40 which is better? I mean,
        as I saw in the requirements, it’s always 8,16,32,64, so I think if you take 40 it will be
        better or 32 or 64, that is, that the gap between them will not change
        the weather or not?</string>
    <string name="question36">Is using multiple servers with 24 threads, say 2 servers 24=48,
        is it the same as using one server with 48 threads?</string>
    <string name="question37">Guys, is there an option like in fish to limit the number
        of threads used?</string>

    <!-- Answers usual. -->
    <string name="answer1">Aleo is the world’s first full-stack development platform for private
        applications (powered by zero-knowledge) with speed, integrity and scale.</string>
    <string name="answer2">Aleo is a protocol that works on the technology of Zero Disclosure -
        ZK (Zero Knowledge). Also, the protocol is programmable, which makes it possible to create
        truly secure programs. The idea of the project is to create an opportunity to create secure
        private applications with zero disclosure (ZK), because such an application will be fast
        and easily scalable.</string>
    <string name="answer3">You can explore all the official links from the start-here channel. There
        is also a curated list of Aleo and Leo code and
        resources made by CTO Howard Wu: https://github.com/howardwu/awesome-aleo</string>
    <string name="answer4">Zero Knowledge Technology (Zero Knowledge) is a technology that allows
        you to confirm any information without disclosing this information.
        For example: Mai has a basket with 7 apples, John can only let Mai into the castle by making
        sure there are 7 apples in the basket, but Mai does not want to show him the contents of the
        basket. ZK makes it possible to confirm Mai`s words without John checking the cart,
        thus skipping Mai.</string>
    <string name="answer5">PoSW (Proof of Succinct Work).</string>
    <string name="answer6">That’s right, Aleo has its own Leo programming language.
        You can read more here: https://www.aleo.org/post/leo-programming-language</string>
    <string name="answer7">That’s right, Aleo has created its own development environment,
        aleo studio: https://www.aleo.studio/</string>
    <string name="answer8">Aleo has a smart contract that allows you to develop applications.</string>
    <string name="answer9">Aleo raised $228 million and was valued at $1.45 billion. Investors: A16z,
        Coinbase Ventures, Polychain, Slow Ventures, zkValidator, Joseph Lubin, Scalar Capital,
        Variant Fund, Galaxy Digital, Placeholder VC, Dekrypt Capital, a_capital, Ethereum Ventures,
        Kora, Softbank, Samsung NEXT and others.</string>
    <string name="answer10">All information https://www.aleo.org/post/aleo-ambassador-program</string>
    <string name="answer11">Articles, memes, infographics, design, graphics, videos, tweets, posters,
        animations, stickers, etc.</string>
    <string name="answer12">In the official Discord of the project in the channel #user-content.</string>
    <string name="answer13">Materials can be found on the official Aleo
        website - https://brand.aleo.org/</string>
    <string name="answer14">There are no exact awards, it was only said that ambassadors will
        be able to get a place on the whitelist, as well as "Aleo Credits".</string>
    <string name="answer15">https://github.com/howardwu/awesome-aleo#wallets here you can
        check it and download.</string>
    <string name="answer16">The date will be announced, it will be possible to buy on Pre-sale.
        Beware of scammers.</string>
    <string name="answer17">Aleo coins will be used to pay transaction fees and are expected to be a
        reward currency for “provers” who will act as L2 providers on top of the network.</string>
    <string name="answer18">With the third round of ambassadors, we are now introducing a third
        group: the voyagers. Think of the voyagers as the “golden apprentices.”
        They create very high-quality content, plan and host Aleo meetups, and actively participate
        inthe community. An ambassador can only become a voyager if they are first an apprentice.
        Similarly, an ambassador can only become a maestro if they are first a voyager.</string>
    <string name="answer19">You can read more about grant program
        here: https://www.aleo.org/post/community-grants-program.</string>
    <string name="answer20">Guide: https://github.com/AleoHQ/snarkOS/
Incentives for Aleo Testnet 3 activated on December 2nd at 00:00 UTC
Testnet 3 Incentives Kickoff: https://www.aleo.org/post/testnet-3-incentives-kickoff
Introducing Provers in Aleo Testnet 3: https://www.aleo.org/post/launching-testnet-3-2-provers
        The official Explorer is in the final stages of development: https://www.aleo.network/
</string>
    <string name="answer21">It is the place where you can learn more about Aleo project and expand
        your expertise in running nodes, leo language, testnet and just become an active member
        of the community, participating in other activities as well.
        Official link to the Aleo education - https://aleoeducation.crew3.xyz/.</string>

    <!-- Answers discord. -->
    <string name="answer22">Hi be active to contribute to the community.</string>
    <string name="answer23">Rather, installing a node on a rented server test no consists of two
        types: the first is installing a node on a rented server, taking into account
        the recommended capacities, the servers cost $ 300 + - the second stage is installing
        a node for mining a farm from video cards, and one person said that he didn’t even
        I will rent an expensive server, because according to the hash rate,
        the video cards will kill those nodes that put the node on the rented server.</string>
    <string name="answer24">When you set up a node, you already create a
        wallet (snarkos account new). The most important thing is to save all the keys and
        the address (well, not necessarily, it will be shown), but be sure to save the keys.</string>
    <string name="answer25">Canva. Adobe Illustrator.</string>
    <string name="answer26">Voyager are ambassadors between Apprentice and Maestro. You can only
        become a Voyager if you have already been Apprentice for at least one round. In each round,
        Maestro earns 50 points, Apprentice earns 25 points, and Voyager earns 40 points (reminder:
        Aleo points have no value of their own).</string>
    <string name="answer27">KYC for the Russian Federation in the block, we already
        have 2 ambassadors unfortunately lost their roles.</string>
    <string name="answer28">Yes, that’s right.</string>
    <string name="answer29">Until January 26, there will be t3 f2, according to the info from the
        last blog article, even if all the tokens do not have time to get it by this number.</string>
    <string name="answer30">On the fireside, they almost always give the opportunity to present the
        project (the only thing left to do is wait for it to happen). At the community call,
        you are unlikely to be able to present (only if you agree on this with Viv or Nodari).
        You can also present in English at our English Speaking Club
        (the date is not yet known).</string>
    <string name="answer31">From what is displayed in the software, there may be some errors on
        the official website. In fact, you have 6k.</string>
    <string name="answer32">Use multiple servers for one wallet? Yes, you can.</string>
    <string name="answer33">I think that 1060 will be very weak.</string>
    <string name="answer34">If we are talking about awards,
        then we initially volunteered and helped the project not in order to receive an award for it.
        This is everyone’s decision. Of course, it’s nice, but getting experience, most often,
        is a hundred times more important than getting something material.</string>
    <string name="answer35">In general, the stronger the iron, the faster.
        I think that 32 and 40, 40 will be stronger.</string>
    <string name="answer36">Need to test. The algorithm is new, while there is little
        statistical data.</string>
    <string name="answer37">No. Here is a different algorithm, the prover usually does not eat all
        the flows. Your kernels generate proof, solve mathematical primitives,
        reaching a certain difficulty target - you can say some level of performance. If 24 cores,
        let’s say, have a performance of 10 conventional units, and 240 cores 100, then the winner
        will be the one who reaches this target and the rewards will be distributed proportionally.
        If your 24 cores do not reach the minimum target value at all, then no rewards
        will be awarded at all.</string>





</resources>